http://www.dinosaurvalley.com/privacy-policy

HomeDrumheller AppAnnouncements@ The PlazaCanada DayMedia ReleasesAbout DrumhellerHistoryStories from the PastNew ResidentsFilm in DrumhellerFilm ListLocations GalleryImportant Film LinksMapsProfileClimateDemographicsEconomic DevelopmentPhoto GalleryTourismGovernmentMayoral and Council History MayorMessage from the MayorMeet the MayorCouncilCouncillors Board and Committee AppointmentsBy-laws and PoliciesCouncil MeetingsCouncil Meeting CalendarPublished AgendaCouncil Meeting MinutesCouncil VideosChief Administrative OfficerMessage from the CAOTown Organization ChartStrategic Business PlanAnnual and Quarterly ReportsFOIPBy-lawsPolicies and ProceduresUseful Government LinksService Capacity Review TendersSnow Removal StrategyCorporate ServicesWater ServicesOpen a Utility AccountConservation TipsMetering and BillingHow to Read my Water MeterHow to Read my Water BillHow to Pay for my Water BillChange Account Info OnlineCemeteryInterment ProcesssPackages and CostsLook for a Loved OneCemetery SearchLicensingBusiness LicenseRegistration ProcessPenalties and FeesPet LicenseProperty AssessmentHow is my Property AssessedDue Date, Penalties and FeesPay Property TaxesHow to Appeal AssessmentLook for my Property OnlineChange Account Information OnlineProperty Tax SearchBudgets and FinancesAccounts Payable and RecievableOnline Accounts PayableOnline Accounts Receivable Tax CertificatesOnline Tax CertificatesCommunity ServicesFCSSLight up the Night ContestFamilyYouthSeniorsDrumheller Community CounsellingValley Growers/Valley Learning GardenHarry Potter Events CommitteeDrumheller Festival of LightsSponsorship OpportunitiesPerformance OpportunitiesVolunteeringVolunteer OpportunitiesMemorial Bench ProgramEconomic DevelopmentProfileEconomic Task Force RecommendationsEnhancements and PartnershipsStart a BusinessFinancial InstitutionsChamber of CommerceBusiness Opportunities New ResidentsWelcoming CommitteeEmergency ServicesMajor EmployersGasTelephone and InternetElectricityWaterEducationMedicalHousingHillsview Phase IIPlanning and DevelopmentSafety CodesBuilding PermitElectrical PermitGas PermitPlumbing PermitPrivate Sewage Disposal PermitDevelopment PermitInteractive MapsDrumheller Public LibraryBusines Opportunities Planning and DevelopmentInfrastructure ServiceBusiness DirectoryAnnual ServicesReport a ProblemWaste ManagementPublic InformationProtective ServicesBy-law Enforcement Animal ControlWeed ControlReport a Problem Emergency ServicesDisaster ServicesFire DepartmentWorkplace Health and SafetyReport a ProblemBadlands Community FacilityBattle of the SexesPlanning a WeddingDrumheller Bridal FairWedding Venue OptionsBanquet HallTerraceCommercial KitchenBook. Request AvailablityPlanning a ConferenceRecreation and FitnessCanalta Fitness CenterHCM Lifestyle Fitness StudioField HouseEncana Running TrackIndoor Play SpaceMembership and AdmissionsDrop-in ScheduleArts and Culture VenuesWestern GM Drumheller Art GalleryCottonwood Clay StudioDrumheller Public LibraryBCF Fundraising CabinetPhoto GalleryAnnouncementsFAQ's BCF Conference PackageCamp BCFParks and RecreationBCF Recreation and FitnessRotary Spray ParkAquaplexBattle of the SexesAmenitiesMembership and FeesCoursesSwimming LessonsSwim ScheduleRequest to Book a PoolPhoto GalleryMemorial ArenaGeneral Rules - ArenaAmenitiesBooking Ice TimeParks and TrailsRecreation Fee Assistance ProgramCareersEmployee BenefitsEmployment OpportunitiesFlood ReadinessHow ToContact Us
Privacy Policy
HomeHomeAPPAnnouncementsAboutGovDeptsHow toBCFRecFlood ReadinessBeHere
Privacy Policy
The Town of Drumheller is dedicated to providing you information that you need about your municipal government without compromising your privacy.
This holds true for the content in the website of the Town of Drumheller and all its subsequent systems and processes.
The Town of Drumheller’s privacy policies are ultimately guided by Alberta’s Freedom of information and Protection (FOIP) Act.
Cookies
Cookies are temporary files that may be saved on your computer while visiting a website. While cookies are use to track visitors of the Town of Drumheller website, your municipal government refrains from storing personal information through them. This information includes:
Browser type;
Screen size;
Traffic patterns, and;
Pages visited.
This information is, furthermore, never disclosed to a third party. Cookies are used strictly for the purposes of analyzing anonymous statistical information in aid of crafting analytics-based strategies for online marketing.
If you wish to reject cookies, however, you may do so by adjusting your web browser’s settings.
Volunteering Personal Information Online
We collect personal information on the Town of Drumheller website only with your consent in the following circumstances:
Directly correspond with us via electronic means.
Accomplish an online form;
Share any of the website’s pages on social media platforms, and;
Request further information on any of our services.
In which case, we keep your information for the possibility of further contact with you if the need arises.
The Town of Drumheller, moreover, refuses to share your information to anyone else and will refrain from sending you information or contacting you outside the scope of your requests.
All e-mail messages are subject to the FOIP Act and Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation.
External Links
Your municipal government’s website links to other sites with which they hold no association.
The Town of Drumheller is not responsible for content found and privacy practices in pages that are linked to the municipal website.
Your municipal government encourages you to examine each external site’s policies and disclaimers prior to the submission of your personal information.
Security and IP Addresses
By visiting our website, the Town of Drumheller will keep track of http requests to its dedicated servers.
These record the visitors IP address or the information automatically assigned by an Internet Service Provider (ISP) to a device requesting a URL.
On this note, IP addresses also archived for systems analysis, maintenance, and site evaluation; however, no attempt is made by your municipal government to identify users unless unauthorized use of the website requires investigation or law enforcement.
HomeDrumheller AppAnnouncementsAbout DrumhellerGovernmentDepartmentsPlanning and DevelopmentBadlands Community FacilityParks and RecreationMedia ReleasesCareersContact Us
HomeAbout UsNewsSearchCareersContact UsDisclaimerTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyStaff
Copyright © 2020.
Dinosaurvalley.com.
Designed & Hosted by MarketingHits.com
×
Covid 19 situation is changing rapidly please check back for further details. Learn more at Drumheller.ca/covid
